{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of House of the Dragon.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is Viserys?",
      "answers": ["King", "Knight", "Priest"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Dragonstone?",
      "answers": ["Castle", "City", "Island"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Rhaenyra?",
      "answers": ["Princess", "Queen", "Lady"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Valyria?",
      "answers": ["Empire", "Kingdom", "City"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Daemon?",
      "answers": ["Prince", "King", "Knight"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Otto?",
      "answers": ["Hand", "Knight", "Scribe"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Targaryen?",
      "answers": ["House", "City", "Dragon"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Alicent?",
      "answers": ["Queen", "Lady", "Princess"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is King's Landing?",
      "answers": ["City", "Castle", "Port"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Corlys?",
      "answers": ["Sailor", "Knight", "Lord"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Iron Throne?",
      "answers": ["Seat", "Title", "House"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Aegon?",
      "answers": ["King", "Prince", "Knight"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Dragon?",
      "answers": ["Beast", "House", "Weapon"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Laena?",
      "answers": ["Lady", "Queen", "Knight"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Ser Harwin?",
      "answers": ["Knight", "King", "Lord"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Pentos?",
      "answers": ["City", "Island", "Castle"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Helaena?",
      "answers": ["Princess", "Queen", "Lady"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Old Valyria?",
      "answers": ["Ruins", "City", "Castle"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is Larys?",
      "answers": ["Spy", "Lord", "Knight"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Westeros?",
      "answers": ["Continent", "City", "Island"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
